Guide to the Western Theater Souvenir Program Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Western Theater Souvenir Program Collection
1922-1994
WA MSS S-3071
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.42
1 box
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of souvenir theater programs for plays set in the trans-Mississippi West, dating from 1921 to 1994. Productions represented include dramas, comedies, and musicals such as Annie Get Your Gun (1946), Bus Stop (1955), Flower Drum Song (1958), Show Boat (1948), and Zoot Suit (1979). The majority of the programs are from Broadway productions, and are dated by year of the New York opening when not indicated on the program. Additional programs represent touring companies of Broadway productions and locally-produced shows including Ramona (Hemet, California, 1939) and Promised Valley (Salt Lake City, Utah, 1947).
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by production title.
Theater -- United States; Western plays; Theater programs -- United States -- 20th Century
- Box listing
  - Annie Get Your Gun, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, 1949 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Greek Theatre, Griffith Park, Los Angeles, California
  - Annie Get Your Gun, 1966 (Box 1)
  - The Bad Man, 1945 (Box 1)
    Los Angeles, California
  - Bus Stop, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Bus Stop, [1955-1956?] (Box 1)
  - Destry Rides Again, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Flower Drum Song, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Destry Rides Again, 1960 (Box 1)
    Touring production
  - Lightnin', 1922 (Box 1)
  - Oklahoma!, 1943 (Box 1)
  - The Most Happy Fella, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Promised Valley, 1947 (Box 1)
    Salt Lake City, Utah
  - The Rose Tattoo, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Ramona, 1939 (Box 1)
    Ramona Bowl, Hemet, California
  - Show Boat, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Show Boat, 1994 (Box 1)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1947 (Box 1)
  - Texas, Li'l Darlin', 1949 (Box 1)
  - The Unsinkable Molly Brown, 1960 (Box 1)
  - The Unsinkable Molly Brown, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Wildcat, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Wildcat, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Zoot Suit, 1979 (Box 1)